- I gotta to work. I'll walk down with you.
- Wait.
(Sheldon:)Uh, which is closer
to the new train store in Monrovia?
The movie theater
or The Cheesecake Factory?
(Howard:)Neither of them are close.
(Sheldon:)I guess it doesn't matter
which one of you drives me.
(Sheldon:)Let's play a fun guessing game
to see who gets to take me.
(Sheldon:)All right. This four-letter word
describes either a printer's type size...
(Sheldon:)...or a compulsion to eat dirt.
- Okay, I'm not driving him.
- Penny, don't give up, you can get this.
(Leonard:)Aren't you going with Sheldon?
(Amy:)No, I have no interest in model trains,
stores that sell them...
(Amy:)...nor their heart-breaking clientele.
(Leonard:)Oh, well, I have some work to do,
so...
(Amy:)I can't imagine that would disturb me.
Carry on.
(Leonard:)Okay. Wouldn't you be
more comfortable at home?
(Amy:)Not really, no.
Alrighty then.
I guess I'll just get started.
(Amy:)Please, I don't need
the running commentary.